ezone.com 2019-10-19

# Ezone Privacy Statement

## Ezone Privacy Statement

Ezone PTY PTD has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website (Ezone.com) and apps.

This site contains links to other sites. Ezone is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites. 

Registering and giving us personal information is not required. 

We don't share specific information with third parties. We don't sell addresses to third parties.

## Third Party Advertising

We use the following third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you use our website and apps:

  * Fyber
  * Google AdSense
  * Chartboost
  * Vungle
  * AppLovin
  * Unity Ads

These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) when you use our website and apps in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, please visit the relevant company websites. Alternatively you can opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalised advertising by visiting: [aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/)

## Cookies

We use cookies and other technologies to enable memberships and certain features of membership (e.g. high score tracking, contest entries, etc). You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features may not function properly as a result.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Children's Guidelines

The Ezone website and apps do: 

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:  [Simon Edis](https://www.ezone.com/feedback.htm) Ezone PTY LTD  Perth, Western Australia
